Rough Ridin' Kids. Two Youngsters With An Eye To
JUstice...And Not Afraid To Fight For It
Buckaroo Sheriff of Texas is a western film directed by Philip Ford.
At the end of the Civil War, Sam White returns home to his ranch in the Texas
ranch -The Panhandle - to find it in the hands of a gang of outlaws
Red White, played by Michael Chapin.
Judy Dawson, played by Eilene Janssen.
Tom White, played by James Bell.
Ted Gately, played by Hugh O'Brian.
Sam White, played by Steve Pendleton.
Betty Dawson, played by Alice Kelley.
Buckaroo Sheriff of Texas is a 1951 American Western film directed by Philip
Ford and starring Michael Chapin, Eilene Janssen and James Bell.
The film's sets were designed by art director Frank Arrigo.